module.exports = [{
    question:'Where do beavers keep their money? ',
    answer:'In the riverbank.'
},{
    question:'I tried asking some beavers to help me build my house',
    answer:'They didn’t give a dam.'
},{
    question:'What did one beaver say to the other at the river?',
    answer:'Dam it'
},{
    question:`Who's the best Canadial singer in Ravage?`,
    answer:'Justine Beaver'
},{
    question:'What did the beaver say to the tree?',
    answer:'It’s been nice gnawing you'
},{
    question:'I asked a beaver out on a date.',
    answer:'the beaver replied: “Gnaw.” I said: “Dam.”'
},{
    question:'Are beavers the best builders in the animal kingdom?',
    answer:'Dam right they are.'
},{
    question:'What do you call a beaver with a bad attitude who acts lazy?',
    answer:'A beaver that doesn’t give a dam.'
},{
    question:'What did the river say when it saw beavers for the first time?',
    answer:'“Well, I’ll be dammed.”'
},{
    question:'The hipster beaver refused to swim in the river.',
    answer:'He said it was too mainstream.'
},{
    question:'What does a French beaver call his dam?',
    answer:'Ma’dame.'
},{
    question:'What is a naughty beavers’ favorite type of wood?',
    answer:'Knotty pine.'
}]
